

#### **PROFILE**

Personal Portfolio (blakelmyers.netlify.app)

10 years as a software engineer

14+ year cancer survovir. Dad x2 cycling enthusiast, Colorado transplant, & avid Cardinals fan

Adaptable, honest, & conscientious; hard worker, congenial, willing to lead, & high aptitude for problem solving

### CONTACT

Address and Cell Number on Request)

blakelmyers@gmail.com

### **EDUCATION**

Washington University - St Louis Graduate Cum Laude Masters in Computer Science 2016

University of Missouri - St Louis Graduated Magna Cum Laude Bachelor in Computer Science, 2011

# **BLAKE MYERS**

#### SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### SKILLS

- C++, C#, JavaScript, Python, HTML, XML, SQL, OpenGL, Java
- DevOps, Agile software development, SAFe
- Git, Jira, Jenkins, Artifactory
- Visual Studio, GLStudio, Blender, WordPress, Xcode, IntelliJ

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### BOEING, SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER JUN 2018 - PRESENT

- Product Owner / SME of Scrum team, responsible for architecture decisions and backlog of tasks
- Developed and coordinated requirements with stakeholders
- Lead and managed a dozen team members working several different projects concurrently
- Developed display software for different mission systems platforms
- Served as mentor to new engineers on code development; also main project lead of code reviews
- Adapted to new architecture and complex code quickly
- Received numerous Boeing Pride awards for outstanding work on assigned projects

# BOEING, MID-LEVEL SOFTWARE ENGINEER JUN 2014 - JUN 2018

- Developed automation tools in C# for data processing
- Led small team in year long project involving new pilot UI for an aircraft platform
- Coordinated target builds and testing for embedded systems
- supported software development on demos involving rapid prototyping for future aircraft capabilities

# BOEING, ENTRY SOFTWARE ENGINEER MAY 2011 - JUN 2014

- Worked on build team, optimizing build scripts and tools
- Developed test and architecture documents, followed by development of code, and integration testing on hardware of real time embedded systems